Guide to the Carolyn Caddes papers and photographs, circa 1980-2015
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Carolyn Caddes papers and photographs, circa 1980-2015
1975- 2015
1982-2003
M0658
Caddes, Carolyn, 1935-
24 Linear feet
Carolyn Caddes (1935- ) is an American photographer who spent years photographing portraits of famous Californian innovators. Her book, Portraits of Success: Impressions of Silicon Valley Pioneers, focused on Silicon Valley technology visionaries such as Steve Jobs, Robert Noyce and David Packard. She spent many hours with each of her subjects and provided an intimate look into their lives. She also conducted extensive research on her subjects’ companies. Portraits of Success was published in 1986 and Caddes did follow up portraits of these pioneers and other technology pioneers on the rise in the mid-1990s for Nikkei, a Japanese business magazine. In the early 2000s, Caddes began another book project. She interviewed and photographed wine makers in Napa Valley. Although this project never became a book, Caddes conducted hours of personal and professional research as well as photographed some of the major contributors in Napa’s wine industry.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
Carolyn Caddes (1935- ) is an American photographer who spent years photographing portraits of famous Californian innovators. Her book, Portraits of Success: Impressions of Silicon Valley Pioneers, focused on Silicon Valley technology visionaries such as Steve Jobs, Robert Noyce and David Packard. She spent many hours with each of her subjects and provided an intimate look into their lives. She also conducted extensive research on her subjects’ companies. Portraits of Success was published in 1986 and Caddes did follow up portraits of these pioneers and other technology pioneers on the rise in the mid-1990s for Nikkei, a Japanese business magazine.
In the early 2000s, Caddes began another book project. She interviewed and photographed wine makers in Napa Valley. Although this project never became a book, Caddes conducted hours of personal and professional research as well as photographed some of the major players in Napa’s wine industry.
Included in this collection are Caddes’ interviews, portraits, research, correspondence and work files depicting Silicon Valley’s technology industry, California wine makers and Caddes’ personal work.
Access Terms
Computers--History.; Computers--Technological innovations.; Engelbart, Douglas Carl, 1925-2013; Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation; Gallo, Ernest; Gallo, Julio; Hewlett-Packard Company--History.; Intel Corporation; Jobs, Steve, 1955-2011; Knuth, Donald Ervin, 1938-; Microelectronics industry--California--Santa Clara County--History.; Mondavi, Robert, 1913-2008; Napa (Calif.); Photographers.; Photography.; Portraits; Reid, Dennis, 1952-; Science--History.; Shockley, William, 1910-1989; Silicon Valley; Stanford University; Terman, Frederick Emmons, 1900-1982; Wine and wine making.; Women photographers; Wozniak, Steve, 1950-
Collection Contents
- Series 1: Portraits of Success: Research and photographs
  - Subseries 1: Portraits of Success: Subjects (Acc # 1989- 123)
  - Adams, Jim, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, clippings and notes.
  - Amdahl, Gene M. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of negatives and portraits of Gene Amdahl. The folder also contains Caddes' notes and correspondence with Amdahl.
  - Atanasoff, John, 1982- 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, correspondence, clippings and notes.
  - Bardeen, John, 1984- 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of negatives and photographs from Bardeen's portrait session with Caddes. The folder also includes correspondence, research and notes from Caddes' interview with Bardeen.
  - Bowers, Albert, 1981- 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of negatives, corrsepondence, clippings and notes.
  - Breiner, Sheldon, 1980- 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of negatives and photographs from Breiner's portrait session with Caddes. The folder also contains correspondence between Caddes and Breiner, newspaper and magazine clippings written about Breiner and Breiner's writings.
  - Bushnell, Nolan, 1984- 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of photographs and negatives from Caddes' portrait session with Bushnell. The folder also includes newspaper clippings, correspondence and notes.
  - Caddes, Carolyn, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of photographs and negatives of Carolyn Caddes.
  - Chodorow, Marvin (Box 1, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes and correspondence.
  - Cook, Paul, 1982- 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, clippings, notes and correspondence.
  - Corrigan, Wilf, 1984- 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Tommy, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, correspondence, notes and clippings.
  - Dennis, Reid W., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes, interview questions and correspondence.
  - Djerasi, Carl, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Draper, William H., III, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes, correspondence and clippings.
  - Dwight, Herbert (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Eckert, Presper, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of negatives, clippings and notes.
  - Engelbart, Doug, 1970- 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Feigenbaum, Edward A., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, articles and notes.
  - Ferrey, Ed, 1982- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes and clippings.
  - Friedenrich, John, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, correspondence and notes.
  - Gibbons, James F., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, clippings, correspondence and notes.
  - Ginsburg, Charles, 1960- 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    The materials consist of company information, negatives, clippings and notes.
  - Ginzton, Edward, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of photogrpahs, negatives, clippings, company research and notes.
  - Grove, Andy, 1984- 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Halperin, Robert M. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives and notes.
  - Hambrecht, William R. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Steve, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of biographical history, notes and clippings.
  - Haughton, Kenneth, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hewlett, William R., 1977- 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hoerni, Jean, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives,correspondence and notes.
  - Hoff, Marcian E. "Ted", 1984- 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hogan, C. Lester, 1971- 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hugle, Bill, 1984- 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of clippings and correspondence.
  - Jobs, Steve (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of photographs and negatives.
  - Jobs, Steve (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of notes, clippings, negatives and correspondence.
  - Johnson, Franklin "Pitch", 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes and biographical information.
  - Johnson, H. Richard, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Reynold, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kay, Alan, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kays, William, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of notes, clippings and biographical information.
  - Kelley, Thomas, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kilby, Jack, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of negatives, notes and a biographical history.
  - Kleiner, Eugene, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes and company information.
  - Knuth, Donald, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kurtzig, Sandra, 1984- 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Linvill, John, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of a biographical history, notes and clippings.
  - Maxfield, Robert R., 1985- 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - McCarthy, John, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, correspondence and a biographical history.
  - McCloskey, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of notes, clippings and a biographical history.
  - McKenna, Regis, 1982- 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - McMurtry, Burton (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Meindl, James, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of correspondence, notes and clippings.
  - Melchor, Jack L., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mineta, Norman, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of clippings, correspondence and notes.
  - Moore, Gordon, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Noyce, Robert, 1983- 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of clippings, notes, correspondence and copies of portraits.
  - Oliver, Barney, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    The materials consist of negatives, correspondence, clippings and notes.
  - Osborne, Adam, 1983- 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    The materials consist of photographs, clippings, notes and negatives.
  - Oshman, M. Kenneth, 1983- 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Packard, David, 1984- 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of clippings, notes, photographs and negatives.
  - Pake, George, 1983- 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of photographs, a biographical history and notes.
  - Panofsky, Adele and Wolfgang, 1983- 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, clippings, correspodence and notes.
  - Perkins, Thomas, 1984- 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Perry, William J., 1984- 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Quate, Cal, 1984- 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rempel, Bob, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of photographs, notes, negatives and correspondence.
  - Riggs (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Robertson, Sandy, 1984- 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rock, Arthur, 1984- 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of clippings, photographs, negatives and notes.
  - Root, L. Eugene, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, company information and notes.
  - Sanders, Jerry, 1984- 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of photographs, clippings, negatives and notes.
  - Schawlow, Arthur L., 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, clippings, notes and correpondence.
  - Shockley, William, 1972- 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, clippings, notes and correspondence.
  - Shugart, Alan, 1983- 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Siegman, Anthony, 1984- 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of clippings, notes and correspondence.
  - Sonsini, Larry, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sporck, Charles E., 1967- 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Swanson, Robert, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of notes, correspondence, clippings and company information.
  - Terman, Frederick, 1977- 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Treybig, James G., 1984- 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Valentine, Donald, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of photographs, notes, company information and correspondence.
  - Varian, Dorothy and and Russell, 1978- 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Watkins, Dean A., undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, notes and biographical history.
  - Whinnery, John, 1979- 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, John A., 1984- 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, correspondencen and notes.
  - Wozniak, Steve, 1984- 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, clippings, correspondencen and notes.
  - Yelverton, Jack, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Young, John, 1983- 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of photographs, negatives, clipping and notes.
  - Zaffaroni, Alex, 1982- 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of negatives, clippings, correspodence and notes.
  - Zschau, Ed, 1984- 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2: Corporation Research (Acc # 1989- 175)
    - Annual Reports: AMD, 1983- 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report: Amdahl, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report: Apple, 1983- 1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report: Ask, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report: Convergent, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports: Dysan, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports: Hambrecht and Quist, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports: Hewlett Packard, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports: IBM, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports: Intel, 1981- 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports: ITT, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports: Measurex, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports: MicroCMOS, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports: National Semiconductor Corporation, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports: Raychem, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports: ROLM, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports: The Signal Companies (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Annual Reports: Spectra- Physics, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Annual Reports: SRI International, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Annual Reports: Stanford University, 1981- 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      The materials consist of financial reports from Stanford's engineering departments and the Center for Integrated Systems.
    - Annual Reports: Syntax Corporation, 1983- 1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports: Tandem, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports: Trilogy, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Apple, 1984- 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of clippings and magazines about Apple Computers.
    - Entrepreneurs, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Fairchild Eight: research, 1984- 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Fairchild Eight: photographs, 1984- 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hewlett- Packard, 1975- 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      The materials consist of clippings, notes, correspondence and photographs.
    - ROLM (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Semiconductor research, 1984- 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Silicon Valley History: clippings and notes, 1982- 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Silicon Valley History: clippings and notes, 1982- 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Silicon Valley History: clippings and notes, 19832- 1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Silicon Valley History: clippings and notes, 1983- 1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Silicon Valley Periodicals, 1984- 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      The materials consist of the following publications: American Electronics Association, Annals of the History of Computing, A Corporate Guide to Business and Electronics.
    - Silicon Valley Periodicals, 1983- 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      The materials consist of Eniac: A Tribute and an issue of Esquire from December 1983.
    - Silicon Valley Periodicals, 1983- 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      The materials consist of National Geographic, Horizons and Solutions magazines.
    - Venture Capitalists, 1983- 1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      The materials consist of clippings and notes.
- Subseries 3: Portraits of Success: Administrative Files (Acc # 1989- 175)
  The materials consist of files pertaining to the publication of Caddes' book Portraits of Success: Impressions of Silicon Valley Pioneers.
  - Acknowledgements, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of a draft of acknowledgements page for Portraits of Success.
  - Ads, notes, brochures, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Advisors, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of notes, correspondence and contact information for the Advisory Committee for Portraits of Success.
  - Appendix, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of a timelines of Portraits of Success subjects.
  - Approval letters, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of approval letters sent to the subjects of Portraits of Success asking them to approve their biographical sketches written by Caddes.
  - Aritcles on Japanese and Chinese Silicon Valleys, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of newspaper and magazine clippings.
  - Bingham, Walter, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of correspondence between Caddes and Walter Bingham about the title of the book.
  - Book Parts, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of a list of book contents.
  - Cards (Questionnaire), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of lists of contacts who answered the questionnaire cards.
  - Check lists, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of check lists of book contents, portraits and index.
  - Cleaver, Dianne, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of correspondence and notes.
  - Cole, Joyce, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    The materials consist of correspondence.
  - Combs, Jo, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Contract, 1985- 1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    The materials consist of files concerning Caddes' book contract.
  - Copy editor, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    The materials consist of files for Caddes' copy editor.
  - Copyright, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    The materials consist of the copyright paperwork for Portraits of Success.
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with publisher, 1986- 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cut Letters, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of letters to subjects whose portraits and biographies were cut from the book.
  - Diary, Stories, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of notes and Caddes' writing about some of the subjects of the book.
  - Discarded information, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of lists and notes that Caddes did not use for the book.
  - Edited bios, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of a few edited biographies of book subjects.
  - Final (3 items), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of mailing receipts, correspondence and notes.
  - Final list, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of lists and information about the book.
  - Foreward, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of documents relating to the foreward of the book.
  - Glaser, Milt, 1984- 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of correspondence and notes between Caddes and Glaser. Glaser helped Caddes design the book.
  - Glossary, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of drafts of the book's glossary.
  - Health care, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of an article about Genetech's gene- splice technology from the October 15, 1985 issue of The Wall Street Journal.
  - Ilford Inc., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    The materials consist of correspondence and an order with Ilford Inc.
  - Index, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    The materials consist of drafts of the book's index.
  - Introduction, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    The materials consist of documents relating to the introduction of the book.
  - Introduction- history and research, 1985- 1986 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    The materials consist of research on Silicon Valley's history used for the book's introduction.
  - Introduction- historical notes and draft, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of notes, historical research and drafts of the book's introduction.
  - Kollings, Pat, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of Pat Kollings' contributions to the book.
  - Larsen, Judith, 1983- 1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of clippings and notes on Judith Larsen, author of Silicon Valley Fever.
  - Lawyers, 1984- 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of correspondence between Caddes and her lawyers.
  - Letter about publisher, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of copies of a letter sent to the book's subjects about the publisher.
  - Lists and suggestions, 1984- 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of lists of subjects and contact information for the book.
  - Maps, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of maps of the Santa Clara Valley.
  - Market research, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of information and notes about the tech market around the world.
  - Master mailing list, 1987- 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of a master mailing list of subjects included in the book.
  - Miller, Wayne, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of correspondence with Wayne Miller.
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Nichols, Luther, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    The materials consist of correspondence with Doubleday publishers.
  - Nilsson, Karen, 1985- 1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - P.A. portraits: executives, 1979- 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Permissions, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of signed release forms from all of the book's subjects.
  - Photocopy of Portraits of Success, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of a second photocopy of the book with notes and comments.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs of a book signing of Portraits of Success.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of photographs from Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: book press, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of correspondence and notes about the book press around Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: book press, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of book press documents including a marketing plan.
  - Portraits of Success: Bookbuilders West Book Show, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of a copy of the Bookbuilders catalog featuring Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: correspondence, 1985- 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of correspondence concerning the publication of Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: documents and notes, 1985- 1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of documents and notes on the publication of Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: documents, notes and slides, 1985- 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of documents, notes and slides pertaining to the publication of Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: documents and photographs, 1985- 1986 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of documents and photographs used for publication in Portraits of Success.
  - Portraits of Success: miscellaneous materials, 1986- 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of negative, personal photographs and personal notes. Also includes the following: information about Portraits of Success on exhibition at the de Saisset Musuem, tributes to Amy J. Blue May 21, 1988 and newspaper clippings along with an issue of Update from the American Electronics Association September 1986.
  - Portraits of Success: newspaper clippings, 1985- 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)